

Personal infoBorn in Terrassa on 03.02.1994

□
 bernatferrerm@gmail.com

+34 601436012

★ Terrassa (Barcelona)

Languages

Programming Languages

PHP Javascript

HTML CSS

SQL Python

Kotlin

Frontend frameworks

Vue React

Full-stack frameworks

Laravel AndroidStudio

Hosting platforms

AWS Google console Heroku

Other tools

Git Linux

Docker Figma

Latex Tableau

Excel Krita

Godot

Soft Skills

- Logical mindset
- Hard working
- Empathic
- Open minded

Interests

- Software development
- Science
- Language learning
- Hiking







Bernat Ferrer

Software engineer, PHP and Javascript

Full-stack web developer with interest for every aspect of software development . Back-end experience with PHP, using architectural patterns like DDD and TDD . Front-end experience with Vue, using vuex as store library and material-ui as main design library. In addition , experience with MYSQL databases, Restful Apis and more.

Professional experience

Full-stack developer at Meetaitech - Barcelona. April 2021 - Now

Currently working at Meetaitech startup. Here, we develop a pioneer product that tracks the online meetings in companies and handles the data produced . My duties here include implementing backend solutions using PHP with Laravel and working with calendar apis like Microsoft graph or google calendar. Also, taking part of the UI design, implementing it using Vue and the Vuex library, managing the Database and maintaining the product.

Fullstack developer at Assembler, Barcelona. June 2020 - Feb 2021

Working with the programming languages HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, SQL and frameworks like Laravel, JQuery and React.

Among other projects, development of a social network with PHP using the Laravel with the main features of a social network. Implementation of a relational database using SQL and database migrations. Usage of MVC pattern with object oriented programming. repo link

Android developer, Barcelona. March 2020 - June 2020

Development of an app for language learning using Kotlin and the MVVM pattern. Published on google play App link.

Data analyst at M-net, Munich. Sept 2018 - Oct 2019

Analysis of revenue data using Tableau and Excel in order to optimize benefits and reduce loses.

Physics Researcher at the USM, Munich. 2018 - 2019

Development of an interface for the visualization of data coming from astrophysical simulations of protoplanetary disks. Name of the master thesis: *Constraints in gap opening timescales in the HD 623296 protoplanetary disk*.

Education

Astrophysics Master Ludwig Maximilians University, Munich (LMU). 2017-2019

Physics Degree Universitat Autónoma de Barcelona (UAB). 2012-2017

Additionally

A user experience course at LMU, Munich. 2019.

A six month internship at the European southern observatory (ESO), Munich. April -Sept 2018.

Volunteer in a homeless shelter in the city of Pittsburgh, USA. Summer 2013.

Private maths teacher for high-school students, Terrassa. 2012-2016.